Guide to the Janet Malcolm Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Janet Malcolm papers
1940-2010
YCAL MSS 935
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
55.67
(59 boxes)
Malcolm, Janet, 1934-
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of research materials, writings, correspondence, vertical files, printed material, audiovisual materials, and electronic media documenting the work and writings of Janet Malcolm. Research materials and writings consist of correspondence, legal documents, transcripts, notes, manuscripts, drafts, proofs, printed material, and other papers created or collected by Janet Malcolm in the course of researching or writing various projects including Psychoanalysis: The Impossible Profession (Alfred A. Knopf, 1981), In the Freud Archives (Alfred A. Knopf, 1984), The Journalist and the Murderer (Alfred A. Knopf, 1990), The Silent Woman: Sylvia Plath and Ted Hughes (Alfred A. Knopf, 1994), The Crime of Sheila McGough (Alfred A. Knopf, 1999), and others. Research materials also include files of correspondence and related papers from J. D. Salinger and Phillip Roth. Vertical files consist of additional writings, correspondence, notebooks, and research materials. Audiovisual materials consist of audiocassettes containing interviews and other recordings generated by Malcolm while conducting research.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Boxes 55-58 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Box 59 (digital media): Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Arrangement
Organized into five series: I. Research materials and writings, 1950-2010. II. Vertical files, 1940-2009. III. Printed materials, 1964-2007. IV. Audiovisual materials, circa 1970s-2005. V. Electronic media, circa 1990s.
Janet Malcolm
Janet Malcolm (born 1934) is an American writer and journalist. A longtime staff writer for The New Yorker and author of numerous books, Malcolm has written on a range of subjects including photography, psychoanalysis, Sylvia Plath and Ted Hughes, and Gertrude Stein and Alice B. Toklas.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Janet Malcolm on the Edwin J. Beinecke Book Fund, 2013.
Authors, American -- 20th Century -- Archives; Women authors; Audiovisual materials; Born digital; Malcolm, Janet, 1934-; Salinger, J. D. (Jerome David), 1919-2010; Roth, Philip
- Research materials and writings, 1950-2010; Series I; 35.67; (40 boxes)
  Arrangement
  Research materials and writings are arranged roughly by project.
  Scope and Contents
  Research materials and writings consist correspondence, legal documents, transcripts, notes, manuscripts, drafts, proofs, printed material, and other papers created or collected by Janet Malcolm in the course of researching or writing various projects. They document the following works: Psychoanalysis: The Impossible Profession (Alfred A. Knopf, 1981), In the Freud Archives (Alfred A. Knopf, 1984), The Journalist and the Murderer (Alfred A. Knopf, 1990), The Silent Woman: Sylvia Plath and Ted Hughes (Alfred A. Knopf, 1994), The Crime of Sheila McGough (Alfred A. Knopf, 1999), Reading Chekhov: A Critical Journey (Random House, 2001), Two Lives: Gertrude and Alice (Yale University Press, 2007), and Iphigenia in Forest Hills: Anatomy of a Murder Trial (Yale University Press, 2011). Also includes research files on the Supreme Court, Ingri Sischy, and other topics, as well as files of correspondence and related papers from J. D. Salinger and Phillip Roth.
  Related Materials
  For related materials, see also Series II. Vertical files.
  - The Journalist and the Murderer, 1970s-1980s (Box 1)
    Correspondence, legal papers, drafts.
  - The Journalist and the Murderer, 1970s-1980s (Box 2)
    Correspondence, legal paper, drafts.
  - The Journalist and the Murderer, circa 1987 (Box 3)
    Transcripts and other legal papers.
  - The Journalist and the Murderer, 1980s (Box 4)
    Research material, correspondence.
  - The Journalist and the Murderer, 1980s (Box 5)
    Research material and drafts.
  - The Journalist and the Murderer, circa 1987 (Box 6)
    Transcripts, legal papers with notes.
  - Salinger and Roth, 1950ss-1990s (Box 7)
    Correspondence, writings by others including correspondence with J.D. Salinger material and Philip Roth material.
  - Reading Chekhov, 2000s (Box 8)
    Research material, correspondence, drafts.
  - Reading Chekhov, 2000s (Box 9)
    Drafts
  - Silent Woman, circa 1991-1995 (Box 10)
    Sylvia Plath and Ted Hughes research material, drafts, correspondence.
  - Silent Woman, circa 1988-1995 (Box 11)
  - Silent Woman, 1980s-1990s (Box 12)
    Research material, writings by others, correspondence.
  - Silent Woman, 1980s-1990s (Box 13)
    Research material, writings by others.
  - Silent Woman (Box 14)
    Correspondence, research material, including a letter from Ted Hughs.
  - Two Lives: Gertrude and Alice, circa 2000s (Box 15)
    Research material, correspondence, writings by others, post cards.
  - Two Lives: Gertrude and Alice, 2000s (Box 16)
  - Two Lives: Gertrude and Alice, 2000s (Box 17)
    Research material, writings by others, correspondence, post cards.
  - The Crime of Sheila McGough, 1980s-1990s (Box 18)
    Research material, transcripts, various legal documents, corrected drafts, various writings.
  - The Crime of Sheila McGough, circa 1990s-2000s (Box 19)
    Legal documents, transcripts, correspondence.
  - The Crime of Sheila McGough, circa 1990s-2000s (Box 20)
  - The Crime of Sheila McGough, 1990s (Box 21)
    Legal documents, transcripts, research material.
  - The Crime of Sheila McGough, 1980s-1990s (Box 22)
  - The Crime of Sheila McGough, 1980s-1990s (Box 23)
    Drafts and legal papers.
  - The Crime of Sheila McGough, 1987-1996 (Box 24)
  - The Crime of Sheila McGough, 1970s (Box 25)
    Drafts, notes and research material.
  - The Crime of Sheila McGough, circa 1990s (Box 26)
  - In the Freud Archives, circa 1990s- 2000s (Box 27)
    Writings including notes drafts and correspondence.
  - Psychoanalysis: The Impossible Profession, circa 1980s (Box 28)
    Manuscript drafts.
  - Godine, Gosse and Collins, 1970s-1980s (Box 29)
    Research material, correspondence, notebooks.
  - Iphigenia in Forest Hills, 2009-2010 (Box 30)
    Drafts, poofs and copies.
  - Nudity, post office, pornography, piece on Penn., 1960s-1990s (Box 31)
    Research material, magazines, writings by others.
  - Supreme Court, 2000s (Box 32)
    Research material, writings by others, transcripts.
  - Supreme Court, 2000s (Box 33)
  - Ingrid Sischy, 1970s-1980s (Box 34)
    Research material.
  - Ingrid Sischy, circa 1970s (Box 35)
    Drafts, transcripts, research material.
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 36)
    Drafts, notes, business files and proofs.
  - Miscellaneous, 1990s (Box 37)
    Drafts and research material.
  - Miscellaneous, 1990s (Box 38)
    Drafts, research material, photographs, writings, correspondence.
  - Miscellaneous, 1990s (Box 39)
  - Miscellaneous, 1950s-1970s (Box 40)
    Drafts, notes and printed material that includes Gargoyle and The New Republic.
- Vertical files, 1940-2009; Series II; 13.42; (12 boxes)
  Janet Malcolm's vertical files were kept in two filing units with three and four drawers, respectively. The arrangement of the files maintains their order by file and drawer as organized by Malcolm.
  Vertical files consists of incoming and outgoing correspondence, writings, writings by others, notebooks, and other papers relating to Janet Malcolm's research and writings.
  For related materials, see also Series I. Research materials and writings.
  - File 1, 1980-2009
    Correspondence, clippings and other material.
    - Drawer 1, 1980s-1990s (Box 41)
      Correspondence by fax and letter includes incoming and outgoing and additional materials.
    - Drawer 2, 1990s (Box 42)
    - Drawer 3, 2000s (Box 43)
      Correspondence by fax and letter includes incoming and outgoing correspondence and additional materials.
  - File 2, 1940-2009
    - Drawer 1, 1940s-1990s (Box 44)
      Correspondence and other materials.
    - Drawer 1, 1980s-1990s (Box 45)
    - Drawer 2, 1990-2006 (Box 46)
      Proofs and proofs with notes.
    - Drawer 2, 1980s-1990s (Box 47)
      Correspondence and research material.
    - Drawer 2, 1990s-2000s (Box 48)
    - Drawer 3, 1980s-1990s (Box 49)
      Correspondence, writings by others, drafts and research materials.
    - Drawer 3, 1980s-2000s (Box 50)
    - Drawer 4, 1980s-2000s (Box 51)
      Writings, drafts, interviews, notebooks and correspondence.
    - Drawer 4, 1980s-2000s (Box 52)
      Writings, drafts, correspondence.
- Printed materials, 1964-2007; Series III; 3.33; (2 boxes)
  Printed materials consist of copies of the New York Review of Books and newspaper and magazine clippings saved by Janet Malcolm.
  - The New York Review of Books, 1984-2007; 2 folders (Box 53)
    Issues with contributions by Janet Malcom.
  - Newspaper and magazine pages and clippings, 1964-1990; 3 folders (Box 54)
- Audiovisual materials, circa 1970s-2005; Series IV; 3.0; (4 boxes); 148
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Arranged roughly in the order in which they were received.
  Audiovisual materials consist of audiocassettes containing interviews and other recordings generated by Janet Malcolm while conducting research.
  - Lucas S., undated; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976507)
    Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Donald [Kuspa?], undated; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976515)
  - Ted [Wong?], undated; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976523)
  - Edit [?]ak, April 26; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976531)
  - Carla R., undated; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976549)
  - Tony, undated; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976556)
  - Sherrie Levine, undated; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976564)
  - Coosje, undated; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976572)
  - Tom McEvilly, undated; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976580)
  - K[?] - Pat Stein, undated; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976598)
  - Kuspit, undated; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976606)
  - A. Michaelson, undated; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976614)
  - Philip Lieder, undated; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976622)
  - Mat K., undated; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976630)
  - Tom McEvilly, undated; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976648)
  - Lucas V?, undated; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976655)
  - Ingrid; two dealers "heartless" and "ruthless, Bank Big[?] card, May 4; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976697)
  - Ingrid, May 6; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976671)
  - Ingrid, 1984 November 7; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976663)
  - Ingrid; grafitti art, December 21; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976689)
  - Ingrid visit; Selena, undated; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976721)
  - Ingrid S. (3) II, January 27; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976713)
  - Ingrid, her resistance, discussion of whether to do piece, May 3; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976739)
  - Ingrid about Richard Serra artwork, 1985 April; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976705)
  - Ingrid, May 22, Summer 1985; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976747)
  - Ingrid wishing no one came to art form and one first issue; Tom MCE brim[?]...end, November 23; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976754)
  - Ingrid, 1986 January 10; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976762)
  - Ingrid, April 27; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976770)
  - Ingrid, January? 18; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976788)
  - Ingrid, May 6; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976804)
  - Ingrid showing me light issue, November 14; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976796)
  - Ingrid talk about visit, one interview, undated; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976812)
  - Ingrid, March 9; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976820)
  - Ingrid, "future of language in Art forum", resistance to reading Art forum; no one seen's Epstein, Ingrid Sischy, May 22; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976846)
  - Ingrid, Hannah Wilke, December 6; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976838)
  - Ingrid visit, Barbara's case, undated; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976853)
    undated
  - Ingrid; one [?] who never gets reviewed in Art forum, 1986 January 5; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976887)
  - Ingrid, How Ingrid met René; Baeth[?] Dali, "the ending", March 9; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976861)
  - Ingrid, November 7; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976879)
  - Ingrid, 1985 January 4 and 11; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976895)
  - Ingrid S. 2nd interview, hiring at Art Forum; turned down, Afort[?]e, Amy, January 20, 1995 April; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976903)
  - Ingrid; Prom queen about my [?] about her, April 23; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976911)
  - Ingrid; Amy, April 23; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976929)
  - Ingrid, beginning discussion of V. Fair, 1985 February 17; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976937)
  - Ingrid; talk about [Maison?], 1985 February 17; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976945)
  - Ingrid, NEA Hu[?] poem [?] right vs left; graffiti art, March 30; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976952)
  - Ingrid, Japan trip, 1984 August 30; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976960)
  - Ingrid; first mention of Se[?], 1985 January 4; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976978)
  - Ingrid; talk about Ingrid's worries about piece, 1986? January 5; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976986)
  - Ingrid Sischy, 2nd interview, detail Witkin, Guggenheim, MOMA, printed material; printed matter (continued), Szakowski job, January 20; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109976994)
  - Ingrid working on Art forum; "disliking mort of what is going on", beggining of NEA story, March 23; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109977000)
  - Ingrid, undated; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109977018)
  - Ingrid; Amy, March 30; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109977026)
  - Ingrid, talk about her lesbianism, 1985 May 16; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109977034)
  - Ingrid, 1986 June 10; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109977042)
  - Ingrid Sischy, interview I, 1984 January 13; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109977059)
  - Ingrid, "you have art" [?] Richard; beginning of feminism talk, April 12; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109977067)
  - Ingrid; talk about her work at Art forum, May 18; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109977075)
  - Ingrid; Ingrid, experiment, René and God, November 30; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109977083)
  - Ingrid S. (3), January 27; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109977091)
  - Ingrid, morning [?], end discussion of piece, February 22; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109977125)
  - Ingrid, March 16; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109977117)
  - Ingrid (2), end of NEA, March 23; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109977109)
  - Ingrid, "revenge", April 12; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109977133)
  - Ingrid visit, end of [foster?] session; Selma to medical students about Billy, undated; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002109977141)
  - S. Abrams, undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975681)
  - Alvarez (1), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975988)
  - Alvarez (2), (3) (1); Anne [Stevenson], telephone (2), (3) (2), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975921)
  - Alvarez (2) (4) (1), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109976143)
  - Alvarez (2) (1), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975939)
  - [Huekowa?], 1997 December 12; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109976176)
  - Carol Hughes (1), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975848)
  - Labowitz (1), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975913)
  - MacDonald (1), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109976093)
  - MacDonald (2) visit, undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109976119)
  - MacDonald (2), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975889)
  - McGinniss (2), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975723)
  - McGinniss (3), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975731)
  - Joe McGinniss; [?] b verdict, guilty, undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975749)
  - Joe McGinniss (4), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975756)
  - Monfredi, undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975715)
  - [Orioles?] (1), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109976028)
  - Petra [?], undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975707)
  - Clarissa Roche (1), [?] on biog, undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975822)
  - Carissa Roche (2), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975855)
  - C. Roche (3); Alvarez (5) (2), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975764)
  - Mark Roch[?] phone, November 5; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975772)
  - J Rose (1), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975970)
  - Rose (2), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975962)
  - Birs S. (2), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109976010)
  - Sh[?] [?], wife (2), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975897)
  - Sheila; Hal Lieberman - notary, May 19; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109976101)
  - Sheila, telephone, May 11; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109976002)
  - Sheila on Bails; Dr. McG[?] (2), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109976069)
  - Sheila Saturday (2) on Bails is common, undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109976085)
  - Sheila (1), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109976135)
  - Sheila (2), 1996 February 21; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975905)
  - Sheila (3), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109976077)
  - Sheila (3); Sheila & Irene (3), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109976044)
  - Sheila & Irene E[?] End; Sheila Sunday End, undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109976051)
  - Sheila - Irene (4), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975780)
  - (Car) Sheila (8), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975699)
  - Elisabeth Sigmund (1), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975798)
  - Elisabeth [Sigmund] (2), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975947)
  - Anne Stevenson (1), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975814)
  - Anne Stevenson (1), second visit, Durham, undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975830)
  - Anne Stevenson (2), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975806)
  - Anne [Stevenson] (2), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975954)
  - Anne [Stevenson] (3), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109976127)
  - Anne Stevenson (4), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109976150)
  - Anne [Stevenson], telephone, April 22; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975863)
  - Anne Stevenson phone, June 19; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109976168)
  - Trevor Thomas (1), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975871)
  - Trevor Thomas (2), From McCullough (1), undated; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109975996)
  - Wyatt, May 20; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002109976036)
  - John Coplons, telephone; Frank Stella, 1986 January 9; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002109977638)
  - Coplons, 2nd interview, undated; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002109977646)
  - Corfer R., 2nd interview, undated; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002109977653)
  - Tom Lawson, undated; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002109977661)
  - Charles Cowles, January 1986; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002109977679)
  - Barbara Rose, 1986 January 9; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002109977687)
  - Corfer R., 2nd interview, Ricard, undated; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002109977695)
  - Rubin, 2nd meeting, undated; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002109977703)
  - Lynda Benglis, undated; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002109977711)
  - Coplons, October 14; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002109977729)
  - Pincus-Wilten, 2nd meeting, undated; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002109977737)
  - Rose II, undated; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002109977745)
  - Rubin, 1985 October; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002109977752)
  - Coplons, interview II, undated; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002109977760)
  - R. Pincus-Wilten, undated; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002109977778)
  - Rubin I, undated; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002109977786)
  - Ulla [Dydo], Ed [Burns], Bill [Rice], April 29; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002109977794)
  - Jellinek (1), undated; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002109977802)
  - Jellinek (2), undated; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002109977828)
  - Jellinek (3), undated; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002109977810)
  - Ulla [Dydo] (2), April 29; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002109977836)
  - Linda Simon II, undated; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002109977844)
  - Ulla [Dydo] and Ed [Burns] (2), 2005 September; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002109977851)
  - Ulla [Dydo] and Ed [Burns], 2005 February; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002109977869)
  - Ulla [Dydo] and Bill [Rice] (1), 2005 September; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002109977877)
  - Joan Ch[?] (2), undated; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002109977885)
  - Joan C., undated; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002109977893)
  - Ulla [Dydo], Ed [Burns], Bill [Rice], 2004 December 2; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002109977901)
  - [Ed] Burns, Ulla [Dydo], Tape 1, 2005 February; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002109977919)
  - Ulla [Dydo] and Ed [Burns], Tape 1, March 25; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002109977927)
  - Ulla [Dydo], Ed [Burns], (2), March 25; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002109977935)
  - Ulla [Dydo], Ed [Burns], Tape 2, 2004 February; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002109977943)
  - Ulla [Dydo] etc., (2), 2004 December 2; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002109977950)
- Electronic media, circa 1990s; Series V; 0.25; (1 box)
  Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - 3 1/2 inch floppy disk labelled "McGough", circa 1990s (Box 59)